## **CONTACT INFO**

#### **PHONE**

+506 8721 9070

#### **EMAIL**

carlos\_retana\_@outlook.com

#### **ADDRESS**

Desamparados, San José, Costa Rica

## **SKILLS**

- Web Development
- Teamwork
- Responsible
- Passion for Al

### **LANGUAGES**

- Spanish native language
- English 60%

#### **WEB RESUME**

carlos-retana.site

# **CARLOS RETANA VIQUEZ**

#### **PROFILE**

I am currently studying systems engineering, I have also trained through courses where I have learned different methodologies. I have experience with CSS3, HTML5 and Javascript, I also have experience with libraries like React and Astro Build.

#### **EDUCATION**

Ingeniería en Sistemas de Computación

2020 - Present

Universidad Fidélitas

**Desarrollo Web** 

Apr 2022 - Dec 2022

Alura Latam - ONE Oracle Next Education

Técnico en Diseño Gráfico

2015 - 2017

Tecnológico de Costa Rica

### **EXPERIENCE**

ABC Design Diseñador Gráfico

2017 - 2019 Corporate identity and

logo design.

Technology used: Illustrator - Photoshop -

InDesign - XD

Vicar Médica Desarrollador Full

Comercial Stac

2023 - Present Front-end and back-end

developer.

Technology used: JavaScript - HTML5 - CSS3